let's discuss the solution for our
performance reporting quiz we need to
check among these all of those that use
quotes from real applications but not
all of the code peak performance doesn't
use any code synthetic benchmarks do not
use code from real applications this is
code specifically designed for testing
application kernels do use code from
real applications but that application
code has been reduced to form a kernel
so this is definitely true an
application suite uses the code from
real applications and uses all of the
code for all of these applications so
this is not true and then an actual
workload mix is similar to an
application suite except that it comes
from usage patterns of a specific user
so the answer to this quiz is that
application kernels use code from your
applications but not all of their code